Good evening, good to see a lot of you. So let's have a quick review of what we talked
about last week. So we talked about three kinds of products last week, a bond, forward
and future. So bond, you know the structure. You are going to receive a huge amount of
money today or you are going to pay a huge amount of money. So the other side of the
mortgage. So you pay a huge amount of money and then you are going to receive a coupon
payment for a fixed period. So say every half year or every three months or something like
that. And then at the end, the maturity day, you will get your principal back. You will
get all your money back. So this is a very safe product. And then we talked about forward.
So if you want to calculate the bond price, you will start to calculating all the future
cash flows, discount all of them to today and then sum them up, you will get the bond
price. So that's how we calculate bond price. So for forward, we go back to this page 16.